

#### CONTACT ME

- Hashoo Boys Hostel, Data Ganj Bakhsh Road, Dhoke Paracha, Rawalpindi
- khalid.ghulbi22@gmail.com
- https://github.com/khalid-akhss19
- in @https://www.linkedin.com/in/ front-end-react-dev/
- +923444804939

### SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• JavaScript
- ••• React.js
- •••• Html and Css
- •••• Bootstrap and Material Ui
- • • Wordpress
- ••• Microsoft Office

## CERTIFICATIONS

- Html and CSS
  Codecademy, freeCodeCamp, w3schools
- Javascript and React.js freeCodeCamp, Udemy
- Python and Wordpress Coursera, DigiSkills
- Networking Essentials
  Cisco Networking Academy

### LANGUAGES

- English
- -Conversational
- Urdu
- -Native/Fluent

# **KHALID HUSSAIN**

# WEB DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a well-organized, self-motivated, and hard-working person. with 1.5+ years experienced as React Developer with exceptional skills in developing responsive websites. I am passionate and enthusiastic to design and develop and have the capability to create extraordinary designs according to the needs and requirements using React concepts and writing application interface code via JavasCript and React JS workflows.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# React Dev(Virtual Intern)

Tech ALPHAlogix (Pvt.) Ltd. | Sep 2022 - present

- Identified web-based user interface and developed highquality responsive user interface
- Translated design into high-quality code and wrote application interface code via javascript following React.js

## Junior React Dev

Webloop.pk | April 2021 - present

- Identified web-based user interface and developed a high-quality responsive user interface
- Wrote application interface code via javascript & React.js

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

#### SZABIST-Islamabad

Bachlors in Computer Science | sept 2019 - june 2023

- Studied C++, Python, java, database and soft skills
- Worked with various projects i.e: Hotel Booking System Using Python, Car Rental System Using C++, University Management System Using C++
- Malaria Identification System using Deep Learning(ongoing)
- Nft Marketplaces, Dashboards, Ecommerce landing page, portfolios

# Aga Khan Higher Secondary School Gilgit

Intermediate in Pre- Engineering | july 2017 - july 2019

- Pre-Engineering
- Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry

## REFRENCES

• Will be furnished upon request.